<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>



  <RulePackDef>
    <defName>SeaShantyDesk</defName>
    <rulePack>
      <rulesStrings>
	<li>description->Sailorman's hymn: Part 1/3; Can you hear the sirens resound? - From the coastline of ireland tonight - It's the song of promising heart - Of the souls that the ocean unite. ~|~ And she stands by the window alone - staring into the rain - she is trying to guide his way home - from the waters that keep them apart. ~|~ So she lights up a candle for hope to be found - captive and blind by the darkness around - firm as a mountain, she never will mourn - timeless awaiting the break of dawn.</li>
	<li>description->Sailorman's hymn: Part 2/3; Can you hear the sailorman's hymn? - as it comes with the rise of the tide - it is sung where the rainbow begins - as a comfort for tears she has cried. ~|~ She remains by the window alone - staring into the rain - she is trying to guide his way home - keeps on praying for god to protect him. ~|~ She lights up a candle for hope to be found - captive and blind by the darkness around - each wave a promise, a new hope reborn - sunrise consoles at the break of dawn.</li>
	<li>description->Sailorman's hymn: Part 3/3; She lights up a candle for hope to be found - captive and blind by the darkness around - firm as a mountain, she never will mourn - timeless! ~|~ She lights up a candle for hope to be found - captive and blind by the darkness around - each wave a promise! ~|~ Sunrise consoles at the break of dawn.</li>

	<li>description->Ode to rum: Verse 1/3; So if all come together, we know what to do! - We all come together just to sing we love you! - And if we all come together, we know what to do! - We all come together just for you!</li>
	<li>description->Ode to rum: Verse 2/3; Racing all around the seven seas - Chasing all the girls making robberies - Causing panic everywhere they go - Party hardy on Titanic!</li>
	<li>description->Ode to rum: Verse 3/3; Sailing, sailing, jumping off the railing! - Drinking, drinking, 'till the ship is sinking! - Gambling, stealing, lots of sex-appealing - Come, let us sing the sailor song!</li>

	<li>description->Pirate I was meant to be: Verse 1/8; We're band of vicious pirates! A sailin' out to sea. When you hear our gentle singing. You'll be sure to turn and flee! - A pirate I was meant to be! Trim the sails and roam the sea!</li>
	<li>description->Pirate I was meant to be: Verse 2/8; "Come on, men! we've got to recover that map!" - "That pirate will be done for, when he falls into our trap!" - We're a club of toneful rovers! We can sing in every clef! We can even hit the high notes! It's just too bad we're tone deaf! - A pirate I was meant to be! Trim the sails and roam the sea!</li>
	<li>description->Pirate I was meant to be: Verse 3/8; "Let's go defeat that evil pirate!" - "We know he's sure to lose, 'cause we know just where to fire at!" - We're thieving balladeers. A gang of cutthroat mugs. To fight us off ye don't need guns! Just really good ear plugs! - A pirate I was meant to be! Trim the sails and roam the sea!</li>
	<li>description->Pirate I was meant to be: Verse 4/8; "All right, crew, let's get to work!" - "Our vocation is a thing we love, a thing we'd never shirk" - We'll fight you in the harbor. We'll battle you on land. But when you meet singing pirates.. "..They'll be more than you can stand." - "Oooh! that was a good one!" - "No, it wasn't."</li>
	<li>description->Pirate I was meant to be: Verse 5/8; "No time for song! We've got to move!" - "The battle will be long, but our courage we will prove!" - We're a pack a' scurvy sea dogs. Have we pity? not a dram! We all eat roasted garlic.. ..then sing from the diaphragm! - A pirate I was meant to be! Trim the sails and roam the sea!</li>
	<li>description->Pirate I was meant to be: Verse 6/8; "Less singing, more sailing." - "When we defeat our wicked foe, his ship he will be bailing!" - If ye try ta fight us.. ..you get a nasty whackin'! If ya disrespect our singin'.. ..we will feed ya to a kraken! - A pirate I was meant to be! Trim the sails and roam the sea!</li>
	<li>description->Pirate I was meant to be: Verse 7/8; "I'm getting so sick of you guys and your rhyming." - "We're ready to set sail, though the cannons need a priming." - We're troublesome corsairs! And we've come to steal your treasures! We would shoot you on the downbeat.. ..but we got to rest five measures. - A pirate I was meant to be! Trim the sails and roam the sea!</li>
	<li>description->Pirate I was meant to be: Verse 8/8; "Stop! Stop! Stop!" - "The brass is what we'll polish and the deck is what we'll mop." - You say you're nasty pirates.. ..scheming, thieving, bad bushwhackers? From what I've seen I tell you.. ..You're not pirates! you're just slacke- A pirate I was meant to be! Trim the sails and roam the sea!</li>

	<li>description->Sailor song: Part 1/3; Sheeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee will kiss 'til your lip bleeds. But she will not take her dress off. Americana, tropicana ~|~ All the sailor boys have demons. They sing "Oh Kentucky why did you forsake me? if I was meant to sail the sea. why did you make me? should've been another state. oh state.. ~|~ 'cause mary anne's a bitch. Mary anne's a bitch. Mary anne's a bitch. Mary anne's a bitch. Mary anne's a bii-iitch!</li>
	<li>description->Sailor song: Part 2/3; Does it matter that our anchors couldn't even reach the bottom of a bath tub? And the sails reflect the moon. It's such a strange job. Playing blackjack on the deck. Still, atop this giant bottle dressed in white. We quietly huddle with our missiles. And we miss the girls back home. Oh home sweet home. ~|~ 'cause mary anne's a bitch. Mary anne's a bitch. Mary anne's a bitch. Mary anne's a bitch. Mary anne's a bii-iitch</li>
	<li>description->Sailor song: Part 3/3; She will kiss until your lip bleeds. But she will not take her dress off. Americana, tropicana, americana, tropicana, americanaaaa, americanaaaaaa..</li>

	<li>description->Shiver my timbers: part 1/3; Shiver my timbers. shiver my soul - Yo oh heave ho! There are men whose hearts are as black as coal - Yo oh heave ho! And they sailed their ship cross the ocean blue. A blood-thirsty captain and a cut-throat crew. Its as dark a tale as was ever told. Of the lust for treasure and the love of gold</li>
	<li>description->Shiver my timbers: part 2/3; Shiver my timbers, shiver my sides - Yo oh heave ho! There are hungers as strong as the wind and tides - Yo oh heave ho! And those buccaneers drowned their sins in rum. The devil himself would have to call them scum. Every man aboard would have killed his mate. For a bag of guineas or a piece of eight. A piece of eight! A piece of eight! five, six, seven, eight! Hulla wacka ulla wacka something not right. Many wicked icky things gonna happen tonight. Hulla wacka ulla wacka sailor man beware. When theres money in the ground theres murder in the air, Murder in the air! One more time now!</li>
	<li>description->Shiver my timbers: part 3/3; Shiver my timbers, shiver my bones - Yo oh heave ho! There are secrets that sleep with old Davy Jones - Yo oh heave ho! When the mainsails set and the anchors weighed. Theres no turning back from any course thats laid. And when greed and villainy sail the sea. You can bet your boots there'll be treachery.. treachery.. treachery..</li>

	<li>description->Drinking song: 1st verse out of 508; Oh, five hundred and eight bottles of beer on the wall, five hundred and eight bottles of beer. You take one down, pass it around. Oh, five hundred and seven bottles of beer on the wall- (repeat until you pass out, or zero has been reached).</li>
	<li>description->Drinking song: 24th verse out of 508; Oh, four hundred eighty four bottles of beer on the wall, four hundred eighty four bottles of beer. You take one down, pass it around. Oh, four hundred eighty three of bottles of beer on the wall- (repeat until you pass out, or zero has been reached).</li>
	<li>description->Drinking song: 259th verse out of 508; Oh, two hundred forty nine bottles of beer on the wall, two hundred forty nine bottles of beer. You take one down, pass it around. Oh, two hundred forty eight bottles of beer bottles of beer on the wall- (repeat until you pass out, or zero has been reached).</li>

	<li>description->Heigh-ho: part 1/3; We drink drink drink drink drink the whole bottle through. To drink drink drink drink drink is what we like to do. It ain't no trick to get wasted quick. if you drink drink drink bottle of rum or grog. it's fine! it's fine! it's fine! it's fine! Where a million pirates dine!</li>
	<li>description->Heigh-ho: part 2/3; We drink drink drink drink drink from early morn till night. To drink drink drink drink drink everything in sight. We drink up bottles by the score. A thousand ales, sometimes more. But we don't know what we drink 'em for. We drink drink drink a-drink drink!</li>
	<li>description->Heigh-ho: part 3/3; Yo ho, heave ho, heigh-ho, heigh-ho, heigh-ho, heigh-ho-rum *whistle*. Yo ho, heave ho! From raids to home we go! *whistle*. Yo ho, heigh-ho heave-ho oh-no!</li>

	<li>description->Drunken Sailor: Part 1/5; What will we do with a drunken sailor? What will we do with a drunken sailor? What will we do with a drunken sailor? Early in the morning; Way hay and up she rises, Way hay and up she rises, Way hay and up she rises, Early in the morning.</li>
	<li>description->Drunken Sailor: Part 2/5; Shave his belly with a rusty razor, Shave his belly with a rusty razor, Shave his belly with a rusty razor, Early in the morning; Way hay and up she rises, Way hay and up she rises, Way hay and up she rises, Early in the morning.</li>
	<li>description->Drunken Sailor: Part 3/5; Put him in the longboat until he's sober, Put him in the longboat until he's sober, Put him in the longboat until he's sober, Early in the morning; Way hay and up she rises, Way hay and up she rises, Way hay and up she rises, Early in the morning.</li>
	<li>description->Drunken Sailor: Part 4/5; Stick him in the scrubbers with a hosepipe on him, Stick him in the scrubbers with a hosepipe on him, Stick him in the scrubbers with a hosepipe on him, Early in the morning; Way hay and up she rises, Way hay and up she rises, Way hay and up she rises, Early in the morning.</li>
	<li>description->Drunken Sailor: Part 5/5; Put him in the bed with the captain's daughter, Put him in the bed with the captain's daughter, Put him in the bed with the captain's daughter, Early in the morning; Way hay and up she rises, Way hay and up she rises, Way hay and up she rises, Early in the morning.</li>
	
	<li>description->Why's the rum gone? Part 1/2; That's not good enough, that's not good enough, that's not good enough, Drinks all around, drinks all around. Why is the rum gone?!</li>
	<li>description->Why's the rum gone? Part 2/2; Why's the rum gone? One! why's the rum gone? Two! One! two! the rum is gone! the rum is gone! Yes! the rum is gone! why is why is why is the rum gone?</li>

	<li>description->Yo ho!: part 1/3; Fifteen men on a dead man's chest, Yo ho ho and a bottle of rum! Drink and the devil had done for the rest, Yo ho ho and a bottle of rum. The mate was fixed by the bosun's pike, The bosun brained with a marlinspike, And cookey's throat was marked belike, It had been gripped by fingers ten; And there they lay, all good dead men, Like break o'day in a boozing ken. Yo ho ho and a bottle of rum.</li>
	<li>description->Yo ho!: part 2/3; Fifteen men of 'em stiff and stark, Yo ho ho and a bottle of rum! Ten of the crew had the murder mark! Yo ho ho and a bottle of rum! Twas a cutlass swipe or an ounce of lead, Or a yawing hole in a battered head, And the scuppers' glut with a rotting red, And there they lay, aye, damn my eyes, Looking up at paradise, All souls bound just contrariwise, Yo ho ho and a bottle of rum.</li>
	<li>description->Yo ho!: part 3/3; Fifteen men of 'em good and true, Yo ho ho and a bottle of rum! Ev'ry man jack could ha' sailed with Old Pew, Yo ho ho and a bottle of rum! There was chest on chest of Spanish gold, With a ton of plate in the middle hold, And the cabins riot of stuff untold, And they lay there that took the plum, With sightless glare and their lips struck dumb, While we shared all by the rule of thumb, Yo ho ho and a bottle of rum!</li>

      </rulesStrings>
    </rulePack>
  </RulePackDef>

</Defs>